Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Questions and answers about the UAW-CIO guaranteed employment plan, 1954; Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Steady work, steady pay, 1955; Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Steward's guide: hints on bargaining and grievance procedures., Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
    Notes: Publication no.318. Copy 2
  - Item 10: The Texas archbishop and the Negro boy, 1954; Publication (Box 82, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Catalog of motion picture films, 1955; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Exhibit 19: what workers thought of the auto industry 20 years ago ..., 1955; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Heritage of hatred: sitdown strike, 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Memo, 1955; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The harvest of the years, 1927; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
    Author: Luther Burbank
  - Item 6: The Political misuse of headlines and news captions: an example taken from 2 Detroit newspapers., 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Correspondence - two, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Here we are: the life, the work, and the times of the people of the UAW in pictures, 1957; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Legislative issues: background notes, 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The ABC of S.U.B.: plans for steady employment: facts about supplemental unemployment benefit plans., 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The Political misuse of headlines and news captions, 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The UAW looks at inflation and administered prices: a portion of the report of UAW President Walter P. Reuther to the Union's 17th Constitutional Convention, Atlantic City, N.J., October 9-16, 1959, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: We remember our past: the UAW is twenty years old, 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Education is not a luxury: a statement, Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The U.S. Government guarantees your right to join a union, 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Ammunition, 1956; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1956 April
  - Item 11: Cast me not off, 1960; Publication (Box 83, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Aim is Prosperity for All - The 1958 Bargaining program of the UAW, Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: By intelligence and faith, 1957; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Author: George Meany
  - Item 3: Heritage of hatred: sitdown strike., 1964; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Instructor's notes for Heart of the Union, 1957; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Solidarity house, 1963; Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Notes: Publication no.342
  - Item 6: The aim is prosperity for all.: The UAW 1958 bargaining program, Publication (Box 83, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The UAW looks at - the atom in peacetime, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The UAW looks at -Workers' stake in world affairs, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Verdict at Kohler, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Action on Taxation, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Carrying on a great tradition: a guidebook for UAW local union editors and publicity chairmen, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
    Notes: Publication no.358
  - Item 6: Cast me not off., 1960; Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Labor news for the U.S., Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Meeting the attitudes of people, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Checklist for local union leaders, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Free labor meets Khrushchev, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The world looks at the UAW, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: UAW what it is, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Union education is vital, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Union eye opener, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Wanted an active education committee, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: A union member speaks to the community, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: How can union education help local union leaders, Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: The UAW looks at - S.U.B., Publication (Box 83, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A guide for local union by-laws, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Education Dept. Materials available to UAW local unions, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Four Presidents speak about the UAW, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A bibliography of education materials, Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A bibliography of education materials: skills for leaders, the issues we face, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Our Past: The challenges ahead, new directions new dimensions, 1985; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Songs for UAW members: Roll the union on, 1986; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The local union Recording Secretary: duties, procedures, guidelines, principles, Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Writing your local union history, 1966; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: You and your membership in the UAW, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A leading American speaks out about unionsJohn W. McCormack, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
    Author: John W. McCormack
  - Item 2: Report of Education Committee - 19th UAW Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: UAW Education Dept. Film catalogue, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Your dues, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: A union summer, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Catalogue of paperback books, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Discussion leaders outline on education and discussion leadership, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Films to build unions, 1964; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Here we are130,000 UAW members..and proud of it!!, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Meeting the attitudes of people, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The President views the UAW, 1963; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: To get actionand communicate ideas, 1960; Publication (Box 84, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Discussion leaders outline for Bargaining as a team, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
    Notes: Training materials
  - Item 2: Discussion leaders outline on Education Methods, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The UAW Home Study Course, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Discussion leaders outline for Steward training, 1962; Publication (Box 84, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The President's job: a guide to the responsibilities and duties of a UAW Local Union President, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: You and your membership in the UAW, 1967; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Notes and Quotes for UAW Campaign Speakers, Oct. 25, 1968 issue, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Ten points for meetings, 1969; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: UAW Ammunition, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.5, 7 (1968:May, July)
  - Item 6: Workers 'Opportunity' College, an associate degree in labor studies, 1969; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: College education financing: UAW members' guide, 1969; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Guide for local union election committee, 1968; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: How to speak at union meetings, Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Notes: Publication no.300
  - Item 10: The outsiders, 1969; Publication (Box 85, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Winning grievances, 1971; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Workers confront education: education confronts workers, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
    Author: Patrcia Cayo Sexton
  - Item 3: You are the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Union is more than engine of equity in shop, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Your UAW dues, it doesn't cost to belong to the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Effective discussion methods: Come now let us reason together, Isaiah 1, 18, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Heritage of struggle: the historic march for justice: sitdown strike., 1977; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Heritage of struggle: the historic march for justice: sitdown strike., 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Is time study scientific?, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Join the war on workplace cancer, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Labor education for this time..., 1977; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Peace among nations and peoples, welcome, John Kerry, Vietnam Veteran, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The hidden story of wages, prices and profits, 1965; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: The UAW's first retirement plan, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The UAW's tuition refund program, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: The union does not pay for any personal expenses, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: This is the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: UAW scholarship programs, Publication (Box 85, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Bargainers are trained, 1972-1974 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Bibliography of education materials relating to skills for leadersthe issues we face, 1975; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: New UAW member orientation-initiation, guide for program planners, 1977; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The First UAW-GM agreement, February 11, 1937, 1977; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The struggle for securityat Chrysler, 30 years after the first strike, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The struggle for securityat Chrysler, a chronology of events, 36 years after the first strike, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The UAWa union that gives service, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: UAW-CAP Council Education Committees, Guide for Action, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Union Education pathway to a better local union, 1976; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: What's the jobof the local union Education Committee?, Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Youand your membership in the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Effective discussion methods: Come now let us reason together, Isaiah 1, 18, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Our union heritage, a chronicle of labor's Struggle for social justice., 1976; Publication (Box 85, Folder 4)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (CIO)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A selected bibliography of education discussion materials available, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Guide for UAW, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Objectives - proposals, policies & guidelines, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Phases of Union Membership, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Union Steward at work, for UAW bargainers, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Workers Opportunity College an Associate Degree in labor studies, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Writing your local union's history, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: You are the UAW, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: You must have factsthe who? What? Why? When? Where?, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Youand your membership in the UAW, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Workers confront education: education confronts workers, 1973; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Your UAW dues, it doesn't cost to belong to the UAW, Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: 10 points for meetings, 1979; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Labor's historic support of public education, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Program workbook for local union education committees: educate new members, train new leaders, unionize the organized, inform the public, get community support: programs to build the UAW, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: The Meeting will come to order: parliamentary procedures, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
    Author: Harold E. Sponberg
  - Item 17: This is the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 85, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Program workbook for local union education committees, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: A call to: Region 4 UAW Women's Seminar on: bargaining and balloting, 1976; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The UAW a union that gives service, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The UAW's first retirement plan, 1974; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The UAW's tuition refund program, 1976; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: UAW film catalog, 1975; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: What every UAW local union representative should know about the UAW, 1975; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: 10 points for meetings, 1979; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Education for a new age, 1975; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Labor education for this time..., 1977; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Letter from Birmingham City Jail, 1982; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
    Author: Martin Luther King
  - Item 12: Our union heritage, a chronicle of labor's Struggle for social justice., 1976; Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The President's job, Publication (Box 85, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Challenges we face as UAW Leaders: Action Issues '78, Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
    Notes: Booklet made up of several instruction pamphlets all bundled together
  - Item 2: Grievance handlers and bargainers pocket guide, 1978; Publication (Box 85, Folder 7)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Announcing the UAW labor book shelf for school libraries, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Education Dept. Materials available to UAW local unions, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Side by... what labor needs, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Teaching high school students about labor unions, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: A Pay check every week of the year, 1952; Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Don't get garnisheed!, 1958; Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Author: Daniel R. Fusfeld
  - Item 7: Employers are sabotaging your security: unemployment compensation is cash in the bank-protect it, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Notes: Publication no.93. Copy 2
  - Item 8: How to win for the union: a handbook for UAW-CIO stewards and committeemen, 1945; Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Hundreds of jobs: a guide to the responsibilities and duties of a UAW-CIO local union president., 1950; Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: What does a Recording Secretary do and how does he do it?, Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Notes: Publication no.182. Copy 2
  - Item 11: You are the UAW, 1972; Publication (Box 86, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The UAW home study course, Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Notes: Made up of training material, all bound together
  - Item 2: Teaching guide for use with AFL-CIO parliamentary procedure manual 'How to run a union meeting', 1959; Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Dept. of Education
    Notes: Publication no. 81.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The UAW home study course, Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Teaching guide for use with AFL-CIO parliamentary procedure manual 'How to run a union meeting', 1959; Publication (Box 86, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The UAW home study course, Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Notes: Made up of training material, all bound together. Copy 2
  - Item 2: A one volume encyclopedia for education committeemen: Building the union, 1949; Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Carrying on a great tradition: a guidebook for UAW local union editors and publicity chairmen, Publication (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Notes: Publication no.358. Copy 2
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Pageant magazine says: in reports from Labor experts across the country, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Running a good union meeting is easy, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO Education Dept., a list of publications, Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: 26 answers to questions about pay and prices, 1945; Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Guide for local union election committee, 1968; Publication (Box 86, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In the great tradition, 11th Convention, UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Notes: Conference booklet
  - Item 2: UAW-CIO - Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO - 'reference' packet, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: UAW-CIO - Steward training, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: UAW-CIO - Time Study, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: UAW-CIO - Union Administration, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: UAW-CIO - Union Social Security, Publication (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Notes: Education materials. 2 copies
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Election Facts, Publication (Box 86, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.3-5 (1952:Oct.)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 1956 Legislative program, Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A program for UAW-CIO members, 1946; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Economic objectives for 1948, Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Recommended UAW 1958 Collective Bargaining Program, Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Resolution on steel strike, 1959; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Statement by the UAW International Executive Board, 1958; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Statement by the UAW International Executive Board on inflation, 1966; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Statement by UAW International Executive Board on preferential hiring, 1956; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: The peaceful uses of East-West trade, 1965; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: UAW Administrative Letter, 1965; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: UAW-CIO Wage Policy Statement, 1946; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: UAW-CIO Wage-Price Policy, 1946; Publication (Box 86, Folder 7)
    Notes: 2 copies
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A UAW-CIO Ammunition Reprint; Political and Paycheck Equality for Women, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Author: William H. Oliver
  - Item 2: A wall map about the report ofthe Committee on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Constitution Committee UAW-CIO Tenth Annual Convention, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Discussion leaders outline - How to run a union meeting, Jay Watkins, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet, 1966; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.20:no.2
  - Item 6: Practicing fair practices in the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprint from September Issue of Ammunition, UAW- CIO
  - Item 7: Statement to the United States Commission on Civil Rights on 'Equality of job opportunity and civil right', 1960; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The fight for majority rule continues, by Paul Sifton, 1953; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The fight for majority rule goes on is pledge made by Senator Lehman, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The state of our union, full employment and fair employment can win for us, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: UAW-CIO wants F.E.P.C., Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Your right to a job, guaranteed by the Illinois Law, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: A bill of rights for all UAW-CIO members, Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Discrimination costs you money, 1947; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Author: Sonya Kaufer
  - Item 15: Handbook for local union fair practices committees., 1961; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. UAW Fair Practices and Anti-Discrimination Dept.
  - Item 16: Justice on the job front, 1947; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Souls don't have color, 1953; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: The ordeal of Bobby Cain, 1956; Publication (Box 87, Folder 1)